[{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":500,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0,0,0,0","clickType":2,"combat":4,"combo":4,"comboTime":"1000,650,600,0","coolTime":"0,0,0,0","effects":"100001,100002,100003,100004","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":0,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":500,"position":1,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":100,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"1000,610,430,700","shakeFront":"170,120,150,500","sn":100001,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":1,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"1500","effects":"100005","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":2,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":8,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":100002,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2500","effects":"100007,100008","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":3,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"800","sn":100003,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":1,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3500","effects":"100009,100011,100012","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":4,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"700","shakeFront":"500","sn":100004,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":1,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3500","effects":"100013","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":5,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":8,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"1000","shakeFront":"170","sn":100005,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":1,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"1500","effects":"100005","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":8,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":100006,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2500","effects":"100007,100008","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101,330201","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"800","sn":100007,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":1,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3500","effects":"100009,100011","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101,330201,330301","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":100008,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0,0,0,0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":4,"comboTime":"667,530,550,0","coolTime":"0,0,0,0","effects":"100101,100102,100103,100104","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":1,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"667,500,550,500","shakeFront":"333,300,430,360","sn":100101,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100105","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":2,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":8,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100102,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100106","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":3,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100103,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100107,100108","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":4,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"600","sn":100104,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100107,100108","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":5,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"600","sn":100105,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100105","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":8,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100106,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100106","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101,330201","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100107,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100107,100108","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101,330201,330301","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"600","sn":100108,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0,0,0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":3,"comboTime":"2300,2100,0","coolTime":"0,0,200","effects":"100201,100202,100203","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":1,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"100,100,1250","shakeFront":"667,500,850","sn":100201,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":true,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"6000","effects":"100204,100208","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":2,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"2500","sn":100202,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"100209,10020501,10020502,10020503","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":3,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"1867","shakeFront":"2100","sn":100203,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"4000","effects":"100206,100210,100201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":4,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"2266","shakeFront":"567","sn":100204,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"100207","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":5,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"150","sn":100205,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100204,100208","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100206,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100205,100209","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101,330201","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100207,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100206,100210","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101,330201,330301","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100208,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"100201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":10,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"1133","shakeFront":"0","sn":100209,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":false,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"100212","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"300","shakeFront":"300","sn":100210,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0,0,0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":3,"comboTime":"1800,1900,0","coolTime":"0,0,200","effects":"100301,100306,100307","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":1,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"360,670,1600","shakeFront":"510,480,400","sn":100301,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100302","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":2,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"1600","shakeFront":"600","sn":100302,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100303","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":3,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"1600","shakeFront":"400","sn":100303,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100304","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":4,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"900","shakeFront":"300","sn":100304,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100305","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":5,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"3000","shakeFront":"1800","sn":100305,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100204,100208","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100306,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100205,100209","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101,330201","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100307,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":2,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":2,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100206,100210","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":3,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"330101,330201,330301","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":100308,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"240101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"420","sn":240101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"240201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"430","sn":240201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"240301","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":240301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"240401,204602","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":240401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"240501,204602","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":240501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"240601,204602","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"200","sn":240601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"340803","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"700","sn":240701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"240801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1000","sn":240801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"240901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"750","sn":240901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"241001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":241001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"241101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"450","sn":241101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"340804","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":7,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"400","sn":241201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"241301","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"360","sn":241301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"3000","effects":"340805","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1000","sn":241401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"240102","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1400","sn":240102,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"240202,100014","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"700","sn":240202,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"240302","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"150","sn":240302,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"240402,100014","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":240402,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"240502","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1260","sn":240502,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"340806","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"400","sn":240602,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"340807","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"760","sn":240702,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"340808","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"800","sn":240802,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"240902","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1200","sn":240902,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"241002","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"600","sn":241002,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"241102","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"850","sn":241102,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"340809","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":7,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1600","sn":241202,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"241302","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"700","sn":241302,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"5000","effects":"241402","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":241402,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"240103,204602","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":240103,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"240203","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1300","sn":240203,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":true,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"240303","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"150","sn":240303,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"240403,100209","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":240403,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"240503,100014","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":240503,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"240603,100014","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":240603,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"240703","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1200","sn":240703,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"240803","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1000","sn":240803,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"240903","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":240903,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"241003","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"900","sn":241003,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"241103,100208","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"300","sn":241103,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"241203","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1900","sn":241203,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"241303,100208","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"1000","sn":241303,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"7000","effects":"241403","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":241403,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"240106","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":240106,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"240206","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":240206,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"240306","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":240306,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"240406","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":240406,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"240506","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":240506,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"240606","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":240606,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"240706","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":240706,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"240906","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":240806,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"241006","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":240906,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"241106","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":241006,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"241206","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":241106,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"241306","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":241206,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"241306","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":241306,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":false,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":false,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"0","effects":"240806","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"0","shakeFront":"0","sn":241406,"snChange":0,"targetType":3,"targetType2":0,"type":0},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"200001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"200101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"200201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"100005","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"200401","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"200501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"200601","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"200701","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":1,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"200901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":200901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"201001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"201101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"201201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":1,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"201401","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"201501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"201601","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"201701","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"201801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"201901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":201901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"202001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":202001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"202101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":202101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"202201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":202201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"240901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":202301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"241001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":202401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"202501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":202501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"202601","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":202601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"202701","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"710","sn":202701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"202801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":202801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"202901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":202901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"203001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":203001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"203101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"650","sn":203101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"700","sn":203201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"203301","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":203301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"203401","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"370","sn":203401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"203501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"620","sn":203501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"203601","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":203601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"203701","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":203701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"203801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":203801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"203901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"750","sn":203901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"204001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":204001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"204101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":204101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"204201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"670","sn":204201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"570","sn":204301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"440","sn":204401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"204501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":204501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"204601,204602","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"400","sn":204601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"204701","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"450","sn":204701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"204801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":204801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"204901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":204901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"205001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":205001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"205101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"710","sn":205101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"205201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":205201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"205301","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":205301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"205401","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"670","sn":205401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"570","sn":205501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"440","sn":205601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"205701","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":205701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"205801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":205801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"205901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"710","sn":205901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"206001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":206001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"206101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":206101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"206201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"670","sn":206201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"570","sn":206301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"440","sn":206401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"206501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":206501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"206601","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":206601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"206701","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"750","sn":206701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"206801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":206801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"206901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":206901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"207001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"670","sn":207001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"570","sn":207101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"440","sn":207201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"207301","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":207301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"207401","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":207401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"207501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"710","sn":207501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"207601","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":207601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"207701","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":207701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"207801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":207801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"207901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"750","sn":207901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"208001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":208001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"208101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":208101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"208201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":208201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"208301","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"650","sn":208301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"700","sn":208401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"208501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"400","sn":208501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"208601","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"670","sn":208601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"570","sn":208701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"340801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":6,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"440","sn":208801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"208901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":208901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209001,204602","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"400","sn":209001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"450","sn":209101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":209201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209301","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":209301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209401","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":209401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"710","sn":209501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209601","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":209601,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209701","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":209701,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209801","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":209801,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"209901","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"710","sn":209901,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"210001","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":210001,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"210101","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":210101,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"210201","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"370","sn":210201,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"210301","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"620","sn":210301,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"210401","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"550","sn":210401,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3},{"active":true,"activeType":1,"atkType":2,"backDis":0,"baseCost":501,"blackTime":0,"canInterrupt":false,"canInterrupted":true,"canMove":false,"casting":"0","clickType":0,"combat":5,"combo":0,"comboTime":"0","coolTime":"2000","effects":"210501","enterScene":false,"hit":false,"isCharge":false,"levelCut":1,"levelLimit":0,"nextChainID":0,"nextChainSn":"","plusCost":501,"position":0,"rageAttack":0,"rageBeAttack":0,"rageKill":0,"range":2.5,"rangeMax":101,"rangeMin":0,"relGeneralSn":"","shakeBack":"500","shakeFront":"500","sn":210501,"snChange":0,"targetType":1,"targetType2":0,"type":3}]